http://www.buckspgl.org/privacy

The Site For Freemasonry in Buckinghamshire supporting the BMCF charity no: 1007193
office@buckspgl.org
HomeCharityCharity NewsMasonic CharitiesCheque PresentationsMCFBMCFBMBFTMFCMHAJoinInterested in JoiningGood ReasonsProceduresEnquire About JoiningWhy JoinNewsNewsIn the PressConcordFreemasonryWhat is FreemasonryHistoryOur MissionPrinciplesWhat We DoQ and AFreemasonry in BucksRoyal Arch ChapterBeyond the CraftProvinceLodgesProvincial TeamProvincial TeamExecutive ResponsibilitiesBookcasePGMs Annual AddressNECC New Masons ClubProvincial UpdatesSecretaries NotesAlmoners ReflectionsCharity Stewards ResumeOrators OfferingsPGO's ClubBucks Masonic WanderersVisiting OfficersRoleBriefingMembers DevelopmentSolomonMembers Development UpdateMaster Elect / Wardens WorkshopsDirector of Ceremonies WorkshopsMentoring ProgrammeSecretaries WorkshopsAlmoners WorkshopsCharity Stewards WorkshopsCombined Classes of InstructionStewards Lecture TeamCentre LocationsUniversity SchemeCommunityIn the CommunityProvincial Shows & EventsCommunity ActivitiesSocialIntroductionProvincial Fund Raising TeamBeaconsfield LadiesBletchley LadiesMarlow LadiesGolf AssociationBowls AssociationClay Pigeon ChallengeContactContactJoin Mailing List
Buckinghamshire Provincial Grand Lodge Data Privacy Statement
Bucks PGL Provincial Website Privacy & Security Policy
Data Controller
You can contact the data controller via email This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Privacy Notice
The Buckinghamshire Provincial Grand Lodge website only retains personal information you have provided.
Why we need your data
We need to know your basic personal data in order to operate an on-going membership organisation and to keep in touch with you. We do not collect any unnecessary personal data from you. Information we collect is shared with the United Grand Lodge of England.
How we use your data
All of the personal data we collect is stored on servers located within the European Union. It is processed by appointed members of Buckinghamshire Provincial Grand Lodge as and when required. It is shared with the United Grand Lodge of England and other approved and affiliated organisations, for example Buckinghamshire Provincial Grand Chapter. Your personal data will not be sold to third parties.
How long we hold your data
Your data is retained for as long as you continue to be a member of the Provincial Grand Lodge of Buckinghamshire or its affiliated Lodges. Certain information may be retained beyond this where legislation requires or for tax purposes.
Your rights
Should you believe any of the information we hold is inaccurate, please contact the data controller (This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.) with details of any amendments. If you wish to raise a complaint about how we have processed your data, please contact the data controller (This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.). If you are not satisfied with our response, you can complain the the information commissioner's office https://ico.org.uk
Cookies and Site Security Certificates
The Bucks PGL website is built on a content management system which utilizes cookies to ensure its correct and reliable operation. You may at your own discretion block these cookies within your browser; however if you do so you may lose particular functionality of this website. To help protect your privacy, certain areas of the site may use secure certificates which ensure an encrypted transmission of data between the website and you. Bucks PGL does not use tracking cookies to monitor your web usage outside of the buckspgl.org domain.
Communicating With Buckinghamshire Freemasons and the General Public
No email is sent to anyone from the Buckinghamshire website with the exception of support accounts. We use only registered opt-in email addressed to send information about important changes to our community and website, and to send notices and other disclosures required by law through a separate system. We instruct all approved communications owners to only use Bcc: in their communications to protect the information of the individual(s) involved and as protection from unauthorized disclosure as part of our overall Privacy Policy. In connection with independent audits of our financial statements and operations, the auditors may seek to contact a sample of our records to confirm that our records are accurate. However, these auditors cannot use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
Disclosure To Unrelated Third Parties
We will not sell or rent any of your personally identifiable information to third parties.
Disclosure Of Payment Details
Our website does not explicitly take any monies for any payments of goods or services. Solely an inspected and trusted third-party site on our behalf handles all payments. If you make a purchase via the payment website, other than to those organizations directly involved in the processing of funds to your bank, your credit card number, bank account and other financial information will never be revealed to any third party except with your express permission or if we are required to do so pursuant to a court order or other legal process
Disclosure Of Information In Response To The Requirements Of Civil Or Criminal Legal Process
We may disclose your personal information including, without limitation, transaction, account information, personal details and the contents of communications if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by (without limitation) the police, security forces, competent governmental, intergovernmental or supranational bodies, competent agencies, departments or regulatory, self-regulatory authorities or organizations or other third parties that we in good faith believe it is appropriate to cooperate with in relation to investigations of fraud or other illegal activity or potential illegal activity, or to conduct investigations of violations of our Terms and Conditions.
Retaining Personal Information
We will retain your personal information for only so long as is necessary for the purposes for which the information was collected or as required for legal purposes. In certain cases, we may keep your information up to 100 years if Principle 5 of the Data Protection Act warrants such retention.
Links To Other Websites
Some pages on the Websites include links to third party websites. Their own privacy statements govern these sites, and we are not responsible for their operations, including but not limited to their information practices. Users submitting information to or through these third party websites should review the privacy statement of these sites before providing them with personally identifiable information.
Changes to this Policy
We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your information and will always be at http://www.buckspgl.org/privacy. By continuing to access or use the Services after any changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.
(Effective from 25 May 2018. Version 6)
HomeCharityCharity NewsMasonic CharitiesCheque PresentationsMCFBMCFBMBFTMFCMHAJoinInterested in JoiningGood ReasonsProceduresEnquire About JoiningWhy JoinNewsNewsIn the PressConcordFreemasonryWhat is FreemasonryHistoryOur MissionPrinciplesWhat We DoQ and AFreemasonry in BucksRoyal Arch ChapterBeyond the CraftProvinceLodgesProvincial TeamProvincial TeamExecutive ResponsibilitiesBookcasePGMs Annual AddressNECC New Masons ClubProvincial UpdatesSecretaries NotesAlmoners ReflectionsCharity Stewards ResumeOrators OfferingsPGO's ClubBucks Masonic WanderersVisiting OfficersRoleBriefingMembers DevelopmentSolomonMembers Development UpdateMaster Elect / Wardens WorkshopsDirector of Ceremonies WorkshopsMentoring ProgrammeSecretaries WorkshopsAlmoners WorkshopsCharity Stewards WorkshopsCombined Classes of InstructionStewards Lecture TeamCentre LocationsUniversity SchemeCommunityIn the CommunityProvincial Shows & EventsCommunity ActivitiesSocialIntroductionProvincial Fund Raising TeamBeaconsfield LadiesBletchley LadiesMarlow LadiesGolf AssociationBowls AssociationClay Pigeon ChallengeContactContactJoin Mailing List
